

Contact

6110-4475

☐ jeffreytiu629@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/jeffreytiu https://jeffreytiu.github.io/

Languages

Cantonese (Native) English (Fluent)

Certifications

Digital Marketing Nanodegree
Intro to Programming
Nanodegree
SEO Fundamentals
Local SEO

Skills

Front-end Development, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, PHP, MySQL, Joomla, WordPress, Opencart, Magento, Bootstrap, Sass, SEO, SEM, Google Analytics, Digital Marketing, MS Office, Adobe Photoshop, Lightroom, Premiere, Autodesk Maya, Photography

JEFFREY TIU

SUMMARY

I am a former Associate at Jessica Chan Real Estate Inc. and in this role I am responsible for a variety of real estate transaction processes and support operations, including: Marketing, Real Estate Photography, Graphic Design, SEO, Web Design & IT Support. Prior to this, I was working as a Web Developer using CMS like Joomla & WordPress and IT Support Technician with over 6 years of combined experiences across these roles.

EXPERIENCE

Jessica Chan Real Estate Inc., Calgary, CA

Associate • July 2016 - August 2019

- Proved real estate photography, HDR blending, photos editing, brochure design & printing. Upload and modified listings onto MLS & our official website.
- Analyzed and modified website content & UX to increase our website SEO, planned and executed SEM to increase web traffic.
- Created and modified campaigns on digital platforms such as Facebook, Instagram and Google AdWords etc.
- Worked closely with advertising companies on regular basis to plan and monitor physical Ads such as Newspaper, Magazine and Flyer.

ONE Concept Group Ltd., Kwun Tong, HK

IT Officer • May 2014 - June 2016

- Provide website design, development and maintenance for the company brands using Joomla and WordPress.
- Develop e-commerce website using Opencart & Magento.
- Provide IT support, video shooting & editing.

Munsang College, Kowloon Tsai, HK

Web Designer • February 2010 - May 2014

- Provide website design, development and maintenance for the college official website and e-learning websites.
- Provide eClass & technical support.

EDUCATION

Leeds Beckett University (2008 – 2010)

BSc (Hons), Multimedia and Entertainment Technology

Hong Kong Institute of Vocational Education (2004 – 2008)

Higher Diploma, Interactive Multimedia and Animatronics